chinaimportal.com 2019-09-14

# Privacy Policy - Chinaimportal.com

Asiaimportal (HK) Limited (the “Company”) is committed to respecting the privacy rights of visitors to its website. This privacy policy explains how we collect, store and use personal data about you when you browse www.chinaimportal.com (the “Website”), purchase one of our services or otherwise provide your personal data to us.

It provides you with details about the types of personal data that we collect from you, how we use your personal data and the rights you have to control our use of your personal data.

This policy applied regardless of how the Website is accessed and will cover any technologies or devices by which the Company makes the Website available to you.

By accessing, browsing or otherwise using this Website, you confirm that you have read and understood this privacy policy. If you do not want your data to be used as set out in this privacy policy, you should not use this Website.

###  What information we collect

#### General Readers’ Information

When you browse the Website we may collect, through analytics software such as Google Analytics, the following personal data about you:

  * Your IP address;
  * Your browsing activities.

#### Comments and Contact Forms’ Information

If you decide to let a comment on our website, we may collect the following personal data about you:

  * Your name, company name and e-mail address;
  * Your IP address;
  * Your website;
  * Your consent to allow us to store the collected data.

If you decide to send an inquiry to us, we will collect all the information asked on the specific contact forms that you will use, which may include:

  * Your name, company name and e-mail address;
  * Your IP address;
  * Your phone number or Skype ID;
  * Your city and/or country;
  * Information concerning the reason you are contacting us;
  * Your consent to allow us to store the collected data, and to send the collected data to a third party agency (only if in the form you require the service of a third party agency recommended by the Company – see our Terms of Service linked below on this page to learn more about this specific point).

#### Newsletter Subscribers and Webinars’ Information

When you subscribe to the Website’s newsletter or one of the webinars offered by the Website (if any Webinar is offered), we may collect the following personal data about you:

  * Your name, company name and e-mail address;
  * Your IP address and / or time zone;
  * Your browsing activities;
  * Your consent to allow us to store the collected data.

Furthermore, if you decide to subscribe to our free newsletter, you’ll receive by e-mail our latest published articles, information about our services, and offer from the agents, developers and other services providers that decide to advertise on the Website.

If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed instructions for unsubscribing at the bottom of each email.

#### Forum Information

When you join our forum, we may collect the following personal data about you:

  * Your name, company name and e-mail address;
  * Your IP address and / or time zone;
  * Your browsing activities;
  * Your consent to allow us to store the collected data.

#### Clients’ Information

When you make purchases from the Website’s E-commerce (including the Services we may provide free of charge), we may collect the following personal data about you:

  * Your name and company name;
  * Your billing address and e-mail details;
  * Your IP address;
  * Your username and password;
  * Your VAT number (if you have one);
  * Your browsing and shopping activities;
  * All the information and files that you send to us through the ticket system located on the ‘My Account’ area;
  * Your consent to allow us to store the collected data.

#### Social Media

If you make use of any social media features on our Website (such as Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn, Google+, Youtube, or others), the social media provider may send us information in line with their policies. That information may include your name, profile picture, gender, friend lists and any other information you have chosen to make available. If you wish to prevent that sharing, you can do so by editing your social media privacy settings or the relevant settings/preferences for other social media providers.

#### Call Monitoring

Calls to and from our customer service may be recorded or monitored for the purpose of quality control and for staff training. Call recordings will be maintained as long as reasonably necessary and will then be deleted. Any personal information obtained from you during the call will be treated in accordance with the provisions of this Privacy Policy.

### How we may store and use your information

The Company (and third party data processors acting on our behalf) may collect, store and process your personal data:

  * to make this Website available to you and to provide you with content which is tailored to your individual tastes;
  * to maintain any registered account that you hold with us;
  * with your agreement, to contact you (by phone call or e-mail) about promotional offers and products and services which we think may interest you;
  * for customer satisfaction and market research purposes;
  * to provide our goods and services to you and for associate purposes, including verifying your identity;
  * for research, analysis, testing, monitoring, risk management and administrative purposes;
  * for any related purposes, or where we have a legal right or duty to use or disclose your information (including for crime and fraud prevention and related purposes).

In addition, we may collect anonymised details about visitors to our Website for the purposes of aggregate statistics or reporting purposes. However, no single individual will be identifiable from the anonymised details that we collect for these purposes.

### How we protect your information

  * We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information (excepted if a third party acquires all or part of our business and/or assets). This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our Website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our Website policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

  * In the event that a third party acquires all or part of our business and/or assets, we may disclose your personal data to that third party in connection with the acquisition.

  * We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.

  * We offer the use of a secure server through PayPal or Stripe. We do not process payment ourselves as, at the moment of purchasing our services, you will be re-direct to PayPal’s website (or buy through Stripe). There, all supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into PayPal’s or Stripe payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

  * After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored in our servers.

### How you can access your information

  * If you subscribed to our newsletter or Webinars, and wish to unsubscribe from e-mail communications that we send to you, you can do this by clicking on the unsubscribe link at the bottom of any e-mail newsletter we have sent.

  * If you want to access, delete or modify the information that you sent using one of the Website’s contact forms (or any comment that you let on the Website), you can sed a request using [this form](https://www.chinaimportal.com/gdpr-request-personal-data/).

  * If you hold an account on the Website (including a forum account), you can access and update your contact information by logging into the ‘My Account’ area using the username and password provided when you opened your account on the Website.

  * If you want to close (or modify) your account on the Website, contact us by using the contact information that you find below on this page. Please also note that we may retain certain information associated with your account, including for analytical purposes as well as for recordkeeping integrity.

  * If you do not hold an account with us (or wish to contact us in relation to any personal information that is not displayed in your account), you may ask us to access, delete or modify the information that we hold about you by using the contact information that you find below on this page.

### Cookie Policy

#### What is a cookie?

In short, a cookie is a small text file that is placed on your computer or mobile device to help ensure that you get the best possible experience when you visit a website.

#### Why does the Website use cookies?

Cookies allow us to improve the Website’s content, functionality and speed, while their tracking ability also helps us to understand your likes and dislikes, which means we can respond quickly and adapt the Website accordingly. We use cookies because it’s important to us that the time you spend on the Website, is as useful and intuitive as possible.

In fact without cookie placement, a website cannot remember your preferences or registration details for your next visit. For example, by allowing us to place cookies in your web browser, you don’t have to remember your username each time you sign in – a cookie helps us to remember that information for you.

The important thing to remember about all of this is that whilst some cookies are used to track your use of our Website, they cannot be used to identify you personally or tell us who you are.

Here’s a snapshot of all of the cookies we use on the Website:

 **First and third-party cookies**

The cookies set by us are called ‘first-party cookies’. Those set by our partners or services we use are called ‘third-party cookies’.

Third-party cookies enable visitors to our website to see and interact with content such as information, services, or videos provided to us by other companies. The same cookies can also help us with website analytics.

 **Session and persistent cookies**

As with most websites, we also use ‘session cookies’, which exist only for the length of time that you visit our site and are deleted once you close your browser, along with ‘permanent cookies’, also known as ‘persistent cookies’, which remain stored on your browser ready for use the next time you visit our website.

 **Essential cookies**

These are required to help you access secure areas (such as your customer account pages) and to use features like our shopping cart. Essential cookies are critical because you can’t access these services without them.

 **Performance and functionality cookies**

These cookies ensure the display of handy features such as videos, banners or popups.

Third-party cookies used in the Website: Youtube, OptinMonster, Deadline Funnel, Leadpages.

 **Analytics and customization cookies**

We use analytics and customization cookies to gather information on how the website is being used by our visitors and to discover how popular our marketing campaigns are. We also use the data we get to help customize the website for you and make the content you see as relevant as possible.

Third-party cookies used in the Website: Google Analytics, Google Adwords, Drip, OptinMonster, Deadline Funnel, Leadpages, Quora, Facebook, Rubicon Project.

 **Social networking cookies**

These cookies allow visitors like you to share our pages and content through third-party social networking websites.

Third-party cookies used in the Website: Google+, Facebook, LinkedIn, Twitter.

#### Remarketing Cookies

We use Third-party remarketing cookies from Google Adwords and Facebook. Remarketing cookies allow us to show our advertisements on Google and Facebook networks to people that visit our Website.

Google may show our ads either on websites that you visit (and that joined Google Adsense program), or on websites owned by Google such as Google.com, Youtube.com, and others.

Facebook may show our ads either on Facebook.com or on websites owned by Facebook, such as Instagram and others.

#### How can you manage or disable cookies?

You can set or amend your web browser controls to accept or refuse cookies whenever you like, but please remember if you do choose to reject cookies, your access to some of the functionality and areas of our Website may be restricted.

Specifically, you can opt out from Google remarketing cookies [here](https://www.google.com/settings/ads), and from Facebook remarketing cookies [here](https://www.facebook.com/ads/preferences/edit/).

Please visit the website [www.aboutcookies.org](https://www.aboutcookies.org/) to learn, in detail, how you can delete and control the cookies that are stored on your computer.

### Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

### California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

  * Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent (excepted if a third party acquires all or part of our business and/or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to that third party in connection with the acquisition).

  * All users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel and going to the ‘My Account’ area.

### Children Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

### Terms of Service

Please also visit our [Terms of Service section](https://www.chinaimportal.com/terms-of-service/ "Terms of service") establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of this Website.

### Visiting our website from outside the United States

If you are visiting our website from outside the United States, please be aware that your information may be transferred to, stored in, and processed in the United States. The data protection and other laws of the United States and other countries that your data may be transferred to might not be as comprehensive as those in your country, but please be assured that we take steps to ensure that your privacy is protected. By using our services, you understand that your information may be transferred to our facilities and those third parties with whom we share it as described in this Policy.

### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our Privacy Policy.

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post the changes on this page.

### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us [through our contact form](https://www.chinaimportal.com/contact-us/ "Contact Us") or by sending an email to info@chinaimportal.com.

 **Last Modification and Review: 17 September 2018**
